Okay so let's start with the leading eye, first oil in your shadows, touch of oil, wipe
that off, okay then we'll look at the shadows, so maybe the, that shadow is probably just
a bit too dark, I'm just gonna lighten that a bit, a bit darker, yeah I'm just gonna lighten
this a bit, get it darker into the corner so I'll use that, okay then we have this
underside of the lid to have a, have a front plane, which is this, and we've got this darker
underside of the lid, so I'm gonna take my ivory, some burnt umber, purple, then
at the underside of the teardot, use some red, alizarin, just on that inside edge,
bit darker, got this, draw this, cano alizarin, on that inside edge, then just on the edge of the
brow, take some mid to dark purple, some burnt umber into that, and then just along this edge,
brow there, got that tone, got a bit darker, okay inside that lid, need to correct that,
I'm gonna go with some orange and red in there, that teardot comes a bit lower, okay,
then looking at the underside of the brow, I'm looking at this shape in here,
gets a bit darker there, what's the same tone, let's up into the brow, get the violet side,
violet orange, get it slightly darker, down here, a bit more red, then goes more the orange side,
orange, I'm gonna start to look at the, just a bit of a transition where the brow turns in,
put a bit more orange in there, okay, got this kind of violet, violet orange,
bit lighter, maybe, so maybe violet yellow, orange, too light in there, okay,
I can pull some of the, that light flesh tone, got some yellow alizarin,
touch of orange, too light, too light, a bit warmer, a bit more orange in there,
I'm just looking at this shape here, okay, just suffering that edge,
I can pull some of that brow shape in there, in that edge, okay, then I pick out some of these,
just going with some violet into that mix, slightly darker, with some orange,
put those little indications in there, okay, looking at the brow, let's look at the,
let's do the, this brow shape, okay, so I'm just going to lighten that,
and then we'll come back into it, and it's like lighter, then I'm going to come in with this
slightly warmer tone, then we can just pick out some of these hairs, just using my
ivory, okay, bring out that shape, put that tone there, okay, so then
across the brow here, slightly warmer shape in there, slightly cooler in here,
bit more on the green side, I'm just going to pick out that, more on the green side,
pick out that highlight, okay, I'm going to take some of that light, shape here, okay,
here, just underneath that brow shape just gets a bit warmer, a little shape in here,
alright, then we've got the the brow on this side, shape here a bit further,
okay, so we've got the brow here, okay, get a slightly lighter, a bit more pink, cross here,
add more yellow to that, now I'm going to look at this edge here,
underneath the brow, add these shapes here, push this edge back a bit, very faint in there,
got that brow shape, let's go into this brow shape here a bit further, okay, the brow shape here
becomes very, comes a bit lighter, this red green, yellow, and this shape in here,
so I'm going to look at the, these shapes around the brow, and then it gets a bit lighter,
so I'll just look at the underside of the brow, a bit lighter in there, and as light as that,
so I've got this, this shape underneath the um, the brow, here this red shape,
just going to put that in, a bit of orangey, just a bit of orange red,
on this one, touch of green, tone that down, okay violet, and tone that down, okay, so where
does that start, just in line with the iris, yeah, okay, got this highlight just underneath the
brow, have like a yellow green, lighten that just a bit more, okay, all right, then I'm going to
darken this a bit more red, and that starts to turn, on the red side, as well as green,
green, yellow, red enough red, okay, more yellow in there, okay, and just here, white,
edge of that lid, okay, I'm just going to, in that edge up there, so that was the um,
that was violet orange, on this edge, okay, then just going to look at that shape in them,
it may have been made that a bit darker, violet orange again, so I'm just looking at this
side of that eye now, this plane, this in the corner of that eye, which is a bit
dark, a bit higher chroma, I'm going to add more red to this violet and orange,
and there's where it starts, on the illusory side, a little like that, a little like that,
and on that edge, I'm just going to pick out this, some of these light shapes, just in the corner there,
right there, like this little illusory crease, shape in there, okay, so now we can look at
some of these accents, on that edge, okay, take some phatalyzerin, some violet
orange, okay, so something like that, and we're going to look at this side here, okay,
so look at the lid, it's on the illusory side, a bit more orange in there say,
if you like, and we start to tear it up, maybe some yellow in there, lighten that up, okay,
then we're looking at this shape in here, so that was a mix of the orange, purple, a bit darker,
that's shadow, put that shape into there for a bit, then shadow, soften that, okay, so then just
underneath the brown there, just gets a bit darker, just in here, get a slightly lighter,
then there's a bit more on the purple side here, on the pink side, a little shade there, okay, so
that's that done, you can look for the separate, the, put the crease in, and so on that down,
some illusory, okay, now I'm going to pick out the highlights on the lid, quite kind of yellowish,
now maybe a touch of green, yellowish, a touch of green, make it a bit lighter, this edge,
okay, looking at the, the underside of the lid now, okay, so I'm going to pick out the
this light shape on her cheek, just picking out that light shape, a bit darker, that eye turns in,
a bit more red, a bit lighter, just looking at some of these lights to begin with,
so I'll pin the T dot, so I think, okay, so then, okay, so still looking at this
eye plane, it turns up into that eye, gets a bit warmer, all right, it's got that corner of the eye,
a bit more pink, there, okay then we've got the, okay, so that light shape, gots into
this around there, then looking at this, so front plane, so that underside of the lid,
a bit more on the orange side, most orange, orange-lizarin, it's in this shape in here,
it's going to be a bit lighter, some green in there, yellow-orange, but more,
so it's more on the red side, I'm going to take the, it's light shape,
I'm going to blend that in, okay, I'll get them where the eye turns in,
so just on the outside of the T dot, it's kind of on the orange side, orange-lizarin,
later, a touch of yellow in there, okay, then the eye turns under, just a bit darker,
around here, okay, underside of the lid, some yellow-green, I'm looking at the underside of the
lid, T dot brings it a bit darker, a bit lighter, then side plane, a bit lighter, okay, then got the
top plane, the lid, there's some-lizarin, a bit of yellow, right to the eye, okay, and I'm just going
to put the iris in, a bit more green, okay, the right to the eye, violet-orange, almost like a
mid-balance of orange, then just put on the slight part of the eye, get it slightly lighter, okay,
so I'm going to pick out the iris, put the pupil in, pick out the iris, some blue, orange, light
blue, pick out the highlight, a second, fix the shadow, the pupil, highlight the light on the lid,
some yellow, T dot, the eye, okay, so that's more or less the eye, finished there.